Jacob Zavita

Irvine, CA (503) 710-5455 jacobzavita@gmail.com

Full Stack Developer with SaaS Sales/Account Management Background

Skillful and dynamic sales professional transitioning to a Full Stack Developer role. Able to successfully build, manage, and grow relationships with key prospects and clients by helping them solve critical challenges in growing their business. Experienced selling consulting, advertising, and SaaS platforms.

- Accomplished \$200k in sales in the first four months at a new company where average acv was \$8k. Also averaged \$50k in monthly upsell where the average account ACV was less than \$20k. Took a company with virtually no sales to \$100k MRR in less than 12 months.
- Utilize a consultative sales approach focusing on the transformation the customer will experience and the long-term business relationship instead of features, benefits, and soundbites.
- Well versed in data cleanliness practices, SFDC admin, sales/martech stacks, and API capabilities.

Professional Experience

Houzz, Irvine, CA

Client Success Manager (2020 - present)

Average 108% to goal on renewal, upsell, and retaining businesses. Responsible for client onboarding and adoption. Drive revenue with upsell and renewing contracts. Help clients solve go-to-market and project management challenges by getting them engaged with Houzz Pro software and advertising program.

SalesProcess.io, Irvine, CA

Account Executive (2019 – 2020)

Prospect, qualify, and close technical founders and CEOs of B2B SaaS startups. Sold over \$200k in the first five-months, exceeding the quota. Create opportunities via outbound prospecting and inbound leads.

Perform qualification calls, present demo explaining how we help them solve critical revenue growth problems. Negotiate the close and arrange for client payment and onboarding.

DiscoverOrg/ZoomInfo, Vancouver, WA

Account Manager/Customer Success Manager (2017 – 2019)

Sold 110% of annual quota and named to the President's Club FY '18. Averaged \$50k monthly in upgrade sales in addition to renewing expiring contracts where the average account ACV was less than \$20k.

Onboarded new customers and be their main point of contact for support, service, and sales. Helped marketing, sales, and recruiting teams follow best practices for leveraging the platform and data. Interviewed end-users to quantify ROI used in my sales conversations with executive decision-makers.

Successfully handled a book of 180 accounts containing over \$3.5M ACV. Focused on both growing accounts expanding in new markets and increasing head-count, and high-risk customers with high-churn risk.

Fleet Logistics, Portland, OR

Head of Sales/Account Executive (2016 – 2017)

Proactively raised the business from virtually no sales to attaining \$100k in monthly recurring revenue (MRR), which enabled the company to attain Series A funding. In three months, developed a provider network from ground-level to 450 freight forwarders. Trained the sales team in Portland and the call center based in Guatemala.

Rider Gudger Consulting, Portland, OR

Co-Founder/Sales and Marketing (2011 – 2016)

Executed product launches for educational and training programs presented by professional speakers and celebrities, including Oprah and New York Times best-selling author Jennifer Lauck.

Participated in funnel building and management activities for consultants. Successfully sold marketing packages ranging from \$10k to \$25k in value.

Education

Bachelor of Science

Sociology
Oregon State University
Corvallis, OR (2010)